=No.9 Hunter=
(Longevity)
(Young Taoist)
(Don't waste a night like this.)
Little Demoness.
What are you going to do?
I will take responsibility for you.
You pesky Taoist!
You...
You've turned into a man?
I...
(Whose face is this?)
(Three Days Earlier)
=Episode 1=
(Demon Realm, Lanruo Hall)
(Lanruo Hall)
(Shangguan Piaopiao, Lanruo Hall Madam)
(Desire is the key to heaven.)
(All demons welcome.)
(Every soul seeks the elixir of ruin.)
Bring forth the courtesan.
Shangguan Ziyan.
They say Lanruo's courtesan
has never taken a guest.
Could tonight be
my lucky night?
One touch from her
and you're in paradise.
I'd die happy just for a taste!
(Shangguan Ziyan, Lanruo Hall courtesan)
Greed. Wrath. Obsession.
Lust. All poison.
You drank them down, craving more.
Now you can be my cure.
(Spirit-Calling Art.)
(Mind snatch. Memory steal.)
(Demon Essence, come forth.)
(Serve my will.)
(Every time I call on the Divine Stone,)
(the Stone Curse awakens,)
(consuming my body.)
(Mortal Realm, Yuanzhen Sect)
(Fasting in solitude.)
(Purging the heart's filth.)
(Blind to karma.)
(Untouched by Love Ordeal.)
(Yuanchu, Taoist of Yuanzhen Sect)
(After a thousand years,)
(why can I still sense her?)
(Gather enough Demon Essence,)
(and I may reach Ninghua Palace.)
(Ninghua Palace)
(Your Majesty,)
(a young demoness begs an audience.)
(She says she's the Saintess's sister.)
(My sister sent word from the Palace.)
(The Demon King Yu Linjun
is the Bitemark Man.)
(Consuming him)
(shall lift my Stone Curse.)
What makes you think you're worthy
of standing before me?
I, Saintess Shangguan Ziyan,
humbly invite Yu Linjun
to grant me Transcendence of Desire.
(Yu Linjun, Demon King)
(A demoness
who wields Spirit-Calling Art.)
(Interesting.)
Come.
(Use Spirit-Calling Art
to check him for bite marks.)
(Nothing?)
(My sister would never lie to me.)
(Why is her spirit here?)
(I'm sorry, Lanxi.)
(I've made you worry again.)
(Shangguan Lanxi, Saintess)
(You're all I have in this world.)
(Whatever it takes,)
(I will break the Stone Curse for you.)
(Find him.)
(Consume him.)
(Live.)
(Live...)
(Ziyan.)
Where is my sister?
She kept calling your name
right up until I ate her.
She was so sweet.
And you
make my mouth water as well.
Once I feast on you,
I'll string you up on the Sacred Tree.
(It turns out
every ornate ornament here)
(is a girl he killed.)
I'm taking your head.
I will make all of Ninghua Palace
pay for my sister!
(Divine Stone Blossoms.)
(She is actually the Divine Stone.)
(She blew herself up
using the Stone's power?)
(This is the last time I help you.)
(She came after all.)
(Why did I fall from the sky?)
(Has the Divine Stone's power
guided me here?)
(The Bitemark Man.)
(I looked everywhere for you.)
(And here you are,
just when I'm about to die.)
(I've run from you forever.)
(Fate still found a way.)
(If the mark shows and I eat you,)
(the Stone Curse will break)
(and my sister will come back.)
(Young Taoist.)
(Think you can take one bite
of twenty years of my power?)
(Thousand-Fold Love Ordeal)
Love,
lose.
(Phantom Yuanchu, Demon Illusion)
Over and over.
You fool!
(Look.)
Love her again,
and you'll never escape.
Stuck forever.
Endless cycles repeat.
No way out!
What should I do, then?
Kill her.
Otherwise you will never master
the complete Wind God Chronicles.
Killing's easy.
Do I really need to teach you?
Kill her.
(Why's he so angry?)
(The bite mark vanished?)
We have never met before.
So why pull a sword on me?
You trapped me with demonic arts,
so you are a demon.
I'm a Taoist.
Killing demons is what I do.
If you were going to kill me,
why stop your sword?
Don't twist my words.
Bound by Four.
I'm choking!
I will die!
Oh, heaven...
I'm stuck! I'm really dying!
Keep your hands off my butt!
Have you no shame?
Forget it, forget it.
We good demons
don't mess with filthy humans.
Still being stubborn?
Hey!
You! Taoist!
Put me down!
Put me down, I said!
Having fun over there, are you?
You won't kill me,
yet you won't set me free.
Are you farming good karma or something?
(What are you hesitating over?)
(This demoness...)
(is the reason you're trapped
in this ordeal.)
(Kill her,
and you'll reach the Perfection.)
(What are you waiting for?)
Yuanchu.
Senior?
Days of fasting. You must be starving.
I brought you so much food!
Aren't you supposed to be with Master?
Why are you back?
I...
(Yuanlang, Yuanzhen Sect Taoist)
You look absolutely mouth-watering.
Oh no, I mean you are beautiful.
You are gorgeous.
The finest candy in the mortal world.
Want some?
Yes, please!
Here.
No.
She's a demon.
I was about to kill her.
Cold-hearted.
Eat first. Kill after.
Oh no, no.
Eat now. Talk later.
Later.
(Yuanchu, Yuanlang, come at once.)
(Important matters to discuss.)
Master.
(Our sect holds the Wind God's power,
hidden from the world.)
(Yuanzhenzi, Yuanzhen Sect Master)
(We've sealed the Sky Rift for ages.)
(But sealing is not healing.)
(Balance remains broken.)
Master.
You called for us?
The Rift is growing.
Creatures are slipping through,
attacking people.
We must find the Divine Stone
to mend the heavens.
Yuanchu, Yuanlang,
you two must set out at once.
Find the Stone.
Mend the heavens and save the world.
Understood.
Where did that young Taoist go?
I must trigger his bite mark soon.
Consuming him will cure my...
(Chi Xiao, Lord Jin'an
Demon Hunting Supervisor)
(Why does he look exactly)
(like Yu Linjun?)
Who are you?
This is not good. Run.
Freeze.
Chi Xiao.
I found a lead on the Divine Stone
at the Demon Hunting Bureau.
I came straight for you.
Divine Stone?
In the Wilds of Lize,
the Divine Stone has appeared.
Xuanwu Sect is hosting
a Grand Demon Hunt.
Word spreads across all lands.
All compete for the Divine Stone.
The Wilds of Lize
is a remote land,
where hell and paradise
stand side-by-side.
To mend the sky and save mankind,
we can't wait.
(There is another Divine Stone
in the mortal realm.)
(If I obtain it,
I can revive my sister.)
I know where it is.
The Stone's location is a secret.
A demon couldn't possibly know.
You preach about saving the world,
but you can't tell good from evil.
My life
is not yours to take.
The mortal world has less justice
than the Void Realm.
(She's exactly the same.)
Demon.
Must die.
I can sense the Divine Stone.
A purple flower blooms on the Stone.
Golden Lotus springs forth
from the earth.
A spiritual root
that blossoms from within.
That flower leads to the Stone.
It's called the Purestone Bloom.
Matches the Bureau's archives.
I've been apart from the Stone for ages.
But now,
only I can sense where it is.
So you can't kill me.
You have to take me with you.
She's got a point.
Demon lies. Don't fall for it.
Why do you want to help us?
What if I said,
I just want to watch you righteous guys
fight over the Divine Stone
and show faces uglier than demons.
Would you believe that?
That's a lie.
I'm doing this for all living beings
in both realms.
What are you doing?
Let go of me.
Our hands lock together.
This chain binds karma,
sharing life and senses.
So you don't hurt anyone.
You said you could find the Stone.
Then prove it.
Fine.
Then you better keep a close eye on me.
Demons are everywhere out there.
The Grand Demon Hunt
is for official Hunters only.
As Supervisor of the Huanxi Kingdom
Demon Hunting Bureau,
I hereby appoint you two
as official Hunters
of the ninth rank.
I accept the commission.
And me?
Demon.
Talk again,
and you die.
Set out!
Wait.
Why keep yelling at her?
Hot, fresh buns.
Eat up before we go.
I'll take one.
Not for those two.
Let's go.
(Yong'an)
Young Taoist.
Hurry up.
Your world's not half bad!
(I have to find a way
to trigger the bite mark.)
You must be hot. Let me fan you.
Let me fan you.
(To be honest,
his collarbones are nice.)
Whatever you're up to,
drop your little schemes.
Or I can kill you anytime.
How could you kill me? I'm...
Remember this:
never reveal your demon form
in front of mortals.
Yuanchu.
Looks like there's a celebration
in the village ahead.
Let's go check it out.
A feast?
Think they'll have braised pork?
Glutton.
Have some decency.
Eating is the most important thing
in the world.
I sense demonic energy!
You fool.
Get out of here fast!
The Ghost Festival
forbids weddings and funerals.
Holding a wedding today...
Something's not right.
This is...
a ghost wedding.
(Young Taoist.)
(With this demon helping me now,)
(I've got you.)
♪I drink the rain of this mortal world,
and seek the path I chose♪
♪How much sorrow and joy have I known?♪
♪With this flesh and blood,
I chase the distant light♪
♪Just to see clearly
the memories of this drifting life♪
♪Let the wind sweep away
this heavy air of sorrow♪
♪Do not forget the tangled paths
that you and I have crossed♪
♪Let towering waves come crashing down,
I'll fight against the tide♪
♪I shatter
the hollow fate they wrote for me♪
♪With a heart free of regret,
I'll face the heavens and earth♪